欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内 字幕广告招租 商业合作Q:1585235535
哲学课本 带了
OK, philosophy book, check.
牙刷 牙膏 带了
And toothbrush, toothpaste, check.
要是你想离家出走
Hey, if you're running away from home,
让你妈咪收拾包裹
letting your mommy pack your bag for you
不是有点破坏效果吗
kind of ruins the shock value.
作为一个走读学生
When you're a commuter student,
我没有宿舍
you don't have a dorm room
可以随时回去拿东西
to go back to and grab anything.
我要用的东西都得带着
Whatever I might need has to be in there
囚为我只要一到学校 就出不来了
since once I get to school, I'm basically stranded.
就像《原始生活》真人秀那样
Oh, so it's kind of like"Naked and Afraid, "
只不过你还有开衫可穿
except you're wearing a cardigan
学生会也有果汁可以喝
and there's a Jamba Juice at the student union.
我甚至带了一个充气枕头
I even take a blow- up pillow
这样课间的时候就能在
so I can relax on the cement bench
喷泉边的水泥长凳上休息了
by the fountain between classes.
如果我把帽子放地上
If I leave my hat on the ground,
还有人会往里扔钱呢
people put money in it.
我也是走读生
I'm a commuter student too.
不过如果某天课多
But sometimes when I have a long day on campus,
我朋友会让我去她们宿舍挤挤
my friends with dorm rooms let me crash there
也不是让
Well, not "let me"
只是她们力气不够大 抬不走我而已
insomuch they're not strong enough to move me.
拜托 这没什么啦
Come on, it's not that bad, right?
你上了大学
You're on campus.
有很多优秀的课程可以上
You got great classes.
还能用小帽子挣钱呢
You're making money with your little hat.
我知道 这没什么
No, it's fine.
如果你受不了 可以告诉我
Well, I mean, if it's not, then talk to me.
我没在抱怨什么 妈
I wasn't complaining, Mom.
只是打算出门了
I'm just trying to get out the door.
你最好别抱怨
Oh, you better not complain.
我昨天给一个人纹泪滴 他一听见警笛声逼近了
Yesterday I tattooed teardrops on a guy who kept saying,
泪滴纹身是比较常见的黑帮/监狱纹身
就开始死命催我
"Can't you go any faster? "
你不能快点儿吗
as the sirens got louder.
这孩子是去上学还是去欧洲徒步旅行啊
Is he is he going to school or backpacking across Europe?
咱们老康纳家没人去过欧洲
Now, no Conner has ever seen Europe,
开着一辆小破卡车到不了的地方
and it's probably not gonna happen
这辈子都别想了
until we can get there in an old pickup truck.
我就知道你在这儿
I knew I'd find you here.
我在外面停车道上都能闻到培根味儿
I could smell the bacon walking up the driveway.
我不是为了培根才来的
I'm not here for the bacon.
我只是想多陪陪家人
I'm here to spend time with my family.
我那外酥里嫩的烟熏肉家人
My crunchy applewood- smoked family.
你怎么来了
Hey, what are you doing here?
我要发泄
I need to vent.
我打算把餐厅打理一下
I'm trying to put everything in order
正式让哈里斯接管
for Harris to start taking over The Lunch Box,
可那些文件也太繁琐了
but the paperwork, it's crazy
营业执照 食品加工许可证
Business license, food handler license,
酒类许可证
liquor permit.
你们根本不知道那人
You have no idea what the man
让我们小店经营者经受了多少折磨
puts us small business owners through.
我知道啊 我开了家五金店
Oh, I do. I run my own hardware store.
我也有我的干墙生意
I have my own drywall business.
我以前管理过高级酒店
Yeah, I used to manage Casita Bonita.
我在明尼苏达开过一家果汁店
I ran an Orange Julius in Minnesota
就不能静静的听我发两句牢骚吗
Sometimes, it's OK to just listen.
有没有人想去
So is anyone interested
不想
Nope.
等我说完
Wait till I ask.
有没有人想去
Is anyone interested
贝弗莉·罗斯的学校
in coming to Beverly Rose's school- -
不想
all: No.
拜托 就没人想要帮助
Oh, come on. Doesn't anyone want to help
一位年轻人改变人生吗
make a difference in a young person's life?
-不想  -想都不用想
all: No. - Hell no.
我需要一位家庭成员
Oh, I need someone in our family
一位有音乐天赋的人去贝弗莉·罗斯的班里讲课
who has musical ability to come teach in Beverly Rose's class.
她们班没有音乐课的预算
They have no arts budget,
可是孩子们的人生中需要音乐
and these kids need music in their lives.
我会弹钢琴
Well, I play piano.
她们把钢琴卖了
They had to sell the piano
换来每个月三十分钟的体育训练
to fund 30 minutes of PE a month
第一节课的内容就是大家一起把钢琴搬走
The first class was the kids carrying out the piano.
我可以教孩子们吹囗琴
I can teach the kids how to play the harmonica.
和朋友们轮流吹着玩很有趣
It's fun passing one around with your friends,
如黑不介意被传染战壕口炎的话
if you don't mind trench mouth.
你呢 露易丝
How about you, Louise?
你会玩吉他 会唱歌 还没有
You play guitar, you sing, and you don't have a disease
纪录片里的那些传染病
from a Ken Burns documentary.
我很乐意
You know, actually, I'd love to
我之前还和丹讨论过 离开这行以后
I was just talking to Dan about how I want to teach music
我想过去教音乐课
now that I'm off the road.
所以你们就
So we're just moving on
自动跳过我了吗
without seeing what Imight have to offer?
抱歉 杰基
Oh, Im sorry, Jackie.
我都不知道你还有什么才艺啊
I didn't know you had any talent.
我高中毕业后在一个即兴乐队里打小手鼓
I played a hell of a tambourine in a jam band
打的那叫一个棒
right after high school.
小手鼓不是什么正儿八经的乐器
Tambourine is not a real instrument.
乐队成员会让他们想睡的姑娘打小手鼓
Bands let the girl they want to sleep with play tambourine
来留住她们
so she won't leave.
怪不得他们把那些
Maybe that's why they took
金属什么的都取掉了
all the little metal things out of it.
坏男生
Those bad boys.
原来他们只想看老娘的诱人身姿啊
They just wanted to see this hot thing shake it.
《康纳一家》是在
The Conners is recorded
现场观众前拍摄录制
in front of a live studio audience.
♪这是正义之锤♪
all: ♪It's the hammer of justice♪
♪是自由的钟声♪
♪It's the bell of freedom♪
♪是一首爱之歌♪
♪It's a song about love♪
♪兄弟姐妹相亲相爱♪
♪Between my brothers and my sisters♪
♪在这片大地上传唱♪
♪AlI over this land♪
再来一遍 所有人 除了贝基
One more, everybody except Becky.
♪在这片大地上传唱♪
all: ♪AlI over this land♪
唱的太棒了 大家
Oh, that was great, everybody.
贝基 把下一首歌的歌词发一下
Becky, can you hand out the lyrics to the next song?
孩子们投入极了
The kids are so into it.
这是沃尔特不用铅笔扎人的记录
This is the longest Walter has gone
保持时间最长的一次
without stabbing anybody with a pencil.
这位是安斯沃思女士 我们的校长
Oh, this is Ms. Ainsworth, the principal.
我有个点子我想和你谈谈
I would love to talk to you about an idea I have
我想开兼职音乐课
for a part- time music program.
我可以一周来几次
I could do it a few days a week.
花不了你什么钱
It would cost you next to nothing.
花不了什么钱的意思是
How next to nothing would you be,
基本上不花钱 还是完全不花钱
right next to it or practically on it?
一点油钱
Gas money.
加上我的午餐
Pay for my lunch.
打印纸或许也会时不时丢几张
Printer paper could go missing now and again.
成交
Deal.
刚刚发下去的
OK, what you have in front of you
是一首特别有趣的歌的歌词
are the lyrics to a really fun song
名叫《舞会皇后》
called "Dancing Queen"
好嘞
OK.
咱们把歌词麻溜收回来
Let's hand back all of these pages.
看都别看
Don't even look at them.
我不小心看了一眼
I accidentally looked at mine.
我会有什么事吗
What's going to happen to me?
没事的 阿尔伯特
You're going to be fine, Albert.
我们马上要上下一节课了
We're just going to let the next class come in.
大家可以稍微早些下课
And all of you are going to have an early recess.
大家解散
Class dismissed.
这首歌怎么了
What's wrong with this song?
我们在家里会跟着跳舞啊
We dance to at home.
我也不知道 亲爱的
I don't know, honey.
你去安慰下阿尔伯特吧
But why don't you go comfort Albert?
记得别用背对着沃尔特
And remember, don't turn your back on Walter.
怎么了
What's going on?
我们很愿意让孩子们多学学唱歌
Look, we would love to have more music for the kids,
但这首歌唱的是一个皇后 有些家长救
but this song is about a queen, and some of the parents
觉得这唱的是变装皇后 会影响孩子的性别认同
are going to interpret that to be about gender identity.
会造成很严重的后果
And then it's going to become a thing.
这太离谱了
This is crazy.
我就是一个家长 我没觉得
I'm a parent, and I don't think
这歌唱的是变装皇后
this song is about a drag queen.
就算是 我也不觉得有什么问题啊
And I wouldn't have any problem if it was.
我也是
Me neither.
可是孩子们回到家
But these kids are going to go home
会告诉家长 他们今天唱了一首
and tell their parents that they sang a song
关于舞会皇后的歌
about a dancing queen.
家长们就会找上学校领导层
The parents are gonna go to the school board.
很快 我的职业生涯就泡汤了
And then pretty soon, I'm looking
只能寻求奥巴马牙科医疗计划
for a new dental plan under Obamacare.
如果你想让学校通过你的音乐课
If you want your program approved by the school board,
就得提前把隐患排除
I'd get ahead of this.
去道个歉
Submit an apology.
天哪 这只是首关于不同人的歌曲而已
God, they're just songs about different kinds of people.
不是说好了
Whatever happened to the love
兄弟姐妹相亲相爱的吗
between our brothers and our sisters?
显然 他们可以想怎么爱就怎么爱
Apparently, they can have all the love they want,
只要兄弟们别穿姐妹们的裙子
as long as the brothers aren't wearing the sisters'dresses.
抱歉我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
我去扔了下垃圾
I had to take out the trash.
多谢你在咱们的约会上邀请了我爸
This was a lunch date, so thanks for inviting my dad.
我欠他一顿饭
Well, I had to buy him lunch.
我打赌输了
I lost a bet.
我高估了自己嘴里
Overestimated how many corn nuts
能塞多少玉米粒
I could fit in my mouth.
我就知道 没有嗨着回到学校食堂
I knew I'd feel weird being back in a school cafeteria
感觉一定会很奇怪
without being high.
所以我买了瓶啤洒
So I brought a beer
你把自己照顾的挺好啊
Oh, well, good for you engaging in self care
你知道这儿不能喝酒吧
You do know that you can't drink in here, right?
咱干这事儿可不是头一次了
This ain't my first rodeo.
下课再还给你
You'll get that back after class.
我刚刚看到马克
So I just saw Mark
从学校心理医生办公室出来
coming out of the school psychologist's office.
你们觉得会不会出什么事了
Do you think I should be worried about that?
在孩子上学的学校工作
I mean, this is the danger of working
就是会有这个风险
where your kid goes to school, right?
总会不小心看到点什么
You're going to see some stuff,
你得假装自己没看到
and you're going to just have to pretend like you didn't.
我就是觉得他心里有事
I just get the feeling that something s bothering him.
我们从前无话不谈
And we used to talk about everything,
可他最近却和我疏远了
and he's being so distant from me lately.
或许他只是想独立一点
Maybe he just wants to be more independent.
他都18了
He s 18
我像他这么大的时候 我都结婚了
When I was his age, I was married
也上班了 自付花销 也会喝酒了
working, paying bills, and drinking beer
我现在就想来两口
which I'd like to do now.
不行
Nope.
可是万一他现在的处境很艰难呢
But what if he's going through something, like, really big?
更糟的是 万一是我造成的呢
Or worse, what if it's something that I did?
亲爱的 你是个很棒的母亲
Honey, you're a great mom.
照我看 他没什么好抱怨的
I can't see where he'd have any complaints.
我就不会有这种担心
That's something I never worry about
因为我了解你妈妈 我本人也是个顶好的家长
because I know your mom and I did a good job as parents
天哪 他不会把这幻想症遗传给我了吧
Oh, my God, am I that delusional?
怎么了
What's up?
我在把碗和碗盖配对
I'm matching up lids and bowls.
帮我看看
Helps me think.
它们的尺寸都不一样
They're all different sizes,
所以我得把所有碗和盖子都试一遍
so I have to try every lid on every container
才能全部匹配上
to find the right bowl.
应该不会很难的
Well, shouldn't be too hard.
我们洗盘子没那么细致
We don't clean the dishes that well.
就把味道闻起来一样的扣上就好
Just match up the lids and bowls that smell the same.
今儿是配盖日吗
It's lid matchup day?
你怎么不叫我 我最喜欢干这个了
Why didn't you call me? I love this.
露易丝 你干嘛呢
Louise, stop.
永远 不要
Never, ever
把不透明的盖子盖在透明盒子上
use opaque lids on transparent containers.
这些盒子只用来装容易腐烂的食物
These are for perishables only
这样就能看到食物是不是坏了
so you can see if something is spoiled.
我不想夸大其词
I don't want to overstate,
但我可能救了谁的命呢
but I may have just saved a life.
这个还是我自己来就好
You know, I'd really rather just do this by myself.
配盖日诶
Ooh, lid day!
我也要来
I'm in.
其实我是来道歉的
I'm actually here to apologize
因为那天学校发生的事
for what happened at school the other day.
怎么了
What's up?
我本来要唱一首阿巴乐队的歌
Oh, I was going to sing an ABBA song,
校长拦住了我
and then the principal stopped me
她觉得家长们
because she thought that the parents
会觉得这样不合适
would find it inappropriate.
等一下
Wait a second.
我上次看的时候 没错 这儿还是美国啊
Last time I looked- - yep, it's still America.
我们不会因为
We don't ban music
不认同歌曲传递的信息就给禁了
just because we disagree with the message.
我们得行动起来
This calls for action.
露易丝 给我一张纸
Louise, I'm going to need a piece of paper.
再来一根笔
I'm going to need a pen.
还要一个很大的橡皮筋
I'm going to need a very large rubber band.
然后再给我一块砖
And I'm going to need a brick
你需要的是冷静点
You need to calm down.
他们不会听我的
They're not going to listen to me.
我也不是学生家长
I don't even have a kid there.
我会和学校道歉
I am going to apologize to the school board
剩下的就交给贝基了
and then just let Becky deal with it.
这是她的战斗
It's her fight.
我看到群消息说今天是配盖日
I saw the group text say it's lid day.
我把和我家的完全匹配不上的
So I grabbed these that don't belong
碗和盖孑拿来了
to anything at our house.
现在不是时候 马克
Not a good time, Mark.
我们说正事呢
We're right in the middle of something here.
我们在谈论贝弗莉·罗斯的学校
We're talking about music being banned
禁止某些歌曲的事
at Beverly Rose's school
他们不让露易丝唱《舞会皇后》
They wouldn't let Louise sing"Dancing Queen. "
听听学校董事会
Have you heard all the other songs
禁止的其他歌曲
the school board's been asked to ban?
约翰·列侬的《想象》拜托
John Lennon's"Imagine"? Come on.
歌词描述了想象世界上没有宗教是什么样子
It has the lyric about imagining no religion.
《劳拉》
"Lola"?
她是跨性别者
She's transgender.
《比莉·珍》
"Billie Jean"?
可能是私生子
Could be the illegitimate kid.
或者只是换了性别的迈克尔·杰克逊
Or- - or just Michael Jackson in general.
《舞出彩虹》《彩虹之上》
"Rainbow Connection. " "Somewhere Over the Rainbow. "
《彩虹之境》
"Rainbowland. "
不能有彩虹
Yep, no rainbows.
赤裸裸的反同
That's just openly anti- gay.
或者反小矮妖
Or anti- leprechaun.
不管怎样 这都是不对的
Either way, it's just wrong.
这太糟糕了
This- - this is horrible.
万一我也是那里的一名学生呢
I mean, what if I'd been a kid in that room?
万一有些孩子的家长是同性恋呢
What if some of these kids have gay parents?
这会让他们怎么想啊
What kind of message is that?
现在不觉得我找砖头的想法疯狂了吧
I guess my brick idea's not looking so crazy now.
你们打算怎么做
What are you going to do?
你知道我支持你
Well, you know I support you.
可是音乐课很重要
But the music program is really important.
音乐改变了我的人生
Music totally changed my life,
那些孩子的人生中也应该有音乐
and those kids deserve the same chance.
我也不知道 要不我回头
I don't know, maybe I'll slip in
偷偷掺进去一首彩虹的歌曲
a rainbow song later on.
但现在我现在不会闹腾
But right now, I'm not making waves.
好吧
OK.
贝基 如果你想抵制 我加入
Well, Becky, if you want to fight this, I'm in.
总有人要付诸行动
Somebody's got to.
我理解这问题与你无关
I understand that this isn't your problem,
但我以为你是个敢想敢做的帅姐们
but I thought you were more of a badass than that.
配盖日都被你毁了
Way to ruin lid day.
嗨 我是达琳
Hi. I'm Darlene.
我在餐厅工作
I work in the cafeteria.
你是学校的心理医生 对吗
You are the school psychologist, right?
是的 我叫卡拉·罗杰斯
Yes. Carla Rogers.
我能坐你旁边吗
Is it OK if I sit with you?
我保证不朝你大倒苦水
Promise not to trauma dump.
所有人都这样说 但一张嘴总是滔滔不绝
Everyone says that, and they do it anyway.
坐吧
Have a seat.
我儿子在这儿上学
So my son goes to school here.
他叫马克·康纳－希利
His name is Mark Conner Healy
你知道他吗
Do you know him?
我不能透露
I can't say one way or the other.
你当然可以说 我们都是
Of course you can. I mean, we're both
学校员工 我们是同事
university employees, colleagues
你好好想想 其实我们的工作性质都是一样的
If you think about it, we both kind of have the same job.
我们挑弄情绪 让一些惹人烦心的事物
We stir things up until something disturbing
浮出水面
comes to the surface.
我发誓不透露任何信息的
I've taken an oath that says I can't divulge anything.
我也发过誓 做个好服务员
Yeah, I've taken an oath too, you know, as a food server.
但如果你来问我
But if you came to me and you wanted to know
辣酱里都放了什么 我会告诉你的
what was in the chili, I would tell you.
我知道那里面都是啥 所以我自带食物
I think I know. That's why I bring my own food.
你得自己找你儿子谈谈
You'll have to talk to your son.
好吧
OK.
不如我告诉你我的猜测
How about I say why I think he came to you,
如果说对了 你就吃一囗
and if I get it right, then you take a bite
你削的非常漂亮的胡萝卜
of one of those carrots you've organized so beautifully.
我儿子没惹麻烦吧
My son is not in danger, right?
太好了
Oh, good.
这是最重要的一点
That is the most important thing.
好了
OK.
他是进入了一个新环境
Is he struggling with his self- confidence
而他父亲在他人生中非常脆弱的时刻抛弃了他
in a new environment because his father abandoned him
而面临着自信心缺失的问题吗
at such a vulnerable point in his life,
即使他的母亲在如此困难的时刻
even though his mother was heroically supporting him
一直英勇无比地支持着他
through such a difficult time?
这就说得通了
Yes! Oh, that makes so much sense.
知道吗作为一个母亲 我会担心这都是因为我
You know, as a mom, you worry that it's something you did.
等等 是我的问题吗
Wait, is it something that I did?
等等 你只是在啃胡萝卜吧
Wait, you're just eating carrots, aren't you?
你在逗我玩呢啊
You're messing with me.
你发的誓言里也有这一条吗
Is that in your Hippocratic Oath?
你的小世界现在不整洁了吧
Oh, your little world's not so tidy now, is it?
我周三下午两点有空
I'm free Wednesdays at 2. 00.
四点行吗 我四点下班
How about 4: 00? That's when I get off.
马克在家吗
Is Mark home?
没有 他应该很快就回来了
No, he should be here any minute.
等等
Oh, but hang on.
你知道不能问他心理咨询的事吧
Now, you know you can t ask him about going to therapy.
我很想尊重他的隐私
Well, I'd like to respect his privacy.
所以我已经从他的心理医生那儿下手了
That's why I tried to shake down his psychologist.
但那个啃胡萝卜的女巫就是不说
But that carrot- eating witch wouldn't crack.
看来得等到下周我去找她做治疗时
I guess we'll get into it when I see her next week
才能知道了
at my session.
在学校怎么样
How was school?
挺好 我有点累了
OK. I was kind of tired.
你看着有点低落
You seem a little down.
是因为我的基因遗传吗
Is that because of the depression
还是我本出自好意的教育
I might have given you either through genes
无意中带给你的抑郁
or my well- intentioned parenting?
什么 没有
What? No.
我只是没睡好
I just haven't been sleeping that well.
你难以安眠 是因为我
You're lying up awake thinking about how I drove
赶跑了你爸 于是你
your father away, and it's left you
无法和别人建立长久的
without the ability to form long, trusting relationships
互相信任的关系吗
with other people?
你怎么回事
What's going on?
是听了什么营销鸡汤书吗
Have you been listening to an audiobook?
没有啊
No.
好吧 我看到你从学校心理医生的
AlI right, look, I saw you coming out of the school
办公室出来
psychologist's office.
我知道不该这样 但我找她聊了聊
And I know it was wrong, but I tried to talk to her.
她什么都没告诉我
I mean, she wouldn't tell me anything- -
你干了什么
You did what?
我们不是说好了 我去你工作的学校上学
Didn't we agree that if I went to school where you work,
你不能干涉我的个人生活的吗
that you weren't going to interfere in my personal life?
我又没签字画押
Yeah, butI didn't sign anything.
你从前遇到麻烦总会告诉我
Look, you always came to me when you had a problem,
可你现在都不怎么和我聊天了
and now you barely talk to me.
-我得知道你是不是还好  -我很好
I need to know if you're OK. I'm OK.
我只是需要有自己的生活
I just want to live my own life.
好吧 我知道了 我越界了
AlI right. Iget it I crossed a line.
对不起 我没必要知道你的情况
I'm sorry. I don't need to know.
我也没必要吃东西 睡觉
I also don't need to eat, and I don't need to sleep.
等我哪天一命呜呼了
And then someday when I'm gone,
你可以对着我的坟偷偷告诉我
you can just whisper it to my grave.
好吧
Fine.
我去找心理医生
I went to the psychologist
是因为我一直都交不到朋友
because I'm having trouble making friends.
我一直都走读上学 感觉自己
And I don't even feel like Im at a university
根本都不像个大学生
because I'm a commuter student.
我原本对上大学期待不已
I couldn't wait to get to college,
现在却只觉得早出晚归像份工作
and now it feels like a job.
你为什么不告诉我呢
Why couldn't you talk to me about that?
因为你已经牺牲了太多了
Because you've sacrificed so much.
我们家明显付不起住宿费
We obviously can't afford for me to move into the dorm,
我不想做个不知感恩的白眼狼
and I don't want to seem like an ungrateful jerk.
不 我不会这样想你的
Well, no, I would never think that.
可是走读真的那么糟糕吗
But is it really that bad being a commuter student?
是啊 大家都有朋友
Yeah. Everybody's making friends
他们下课后会一起在宿舍吃喝玩乐
cause they're hanging out in their dorms after classes.
学校晚间还有很多活动
And there's all this cool stuff in the evening
有戏剧表演 冷知识轰趴
like theater and trivia.
我都不能加入性少数者联盟
And I can't join the LGBTQ alliance
因为他们只在晚上焦会
because they only meet at night.
我连做同性恋的机会都没有
I don't even have time to be gay.
要不你每天早起一会儿
OK, how about you wake up earlier,
自己享受一小时同性恋时光
and then you get an hour of gay time for yourself.
多谢 看来我只能自己学着适应了
Thanks for the tip, but I'll learn to live with it.
别啊
No, come on.
我们总得想出个
I mean, we've got to be able to come up
更好的办法吧
with something better than that.
我说了 没关系的
Hey, I'm telling you, it's OK.
在应付苦痛人生这方面
When it comes to dealing with being miserable,
咱们家全是我的表率
I have a house full of role models.
我知道我们看上去活的很轻松
I know we make it look easy, but don't beat yourself up
但你现在学不会苦中作乐也不用自责
if you're not unhappy right away.
相信我
Just trust me.
会有那一天的
It'll happen.
♪我一直在追寻♪
♪I'm always chasing♪
♪彩虹♪
♪Rainbows♪
你来干嘛
What are you doing here?
我也想问你
I'd ask you the same.
但这已经很明显 不用问了
But it s not subtle enough to need an explanation.
不过我喜欢你的作风
Like it, though.
你不是该在家练习怎么道歉吗
I thought you'd be home working on your apology.
还是你需要先列一份道歉注意事顶清单
Or do you need a preapproved list of apologjes
免得冒犯到别人
so you don't offend anybody?
我不会去道歉的
I'm not apologizing.
你们把我骂的狗血淋头 我也正需要这个
You guys really kicked my ass, and I needed it
留下一堆烂摊子
It's easy to drop the ball
给别人收拾很简单
and let someone else pick it up.
我从没这样做过
I have never done that.
我现在也不打算这样做
Not going to start now.
配盖日的精神就是这样嘛
That's what lid day is all aboutl
真可惜
Oh, it's a shame
孩子们没有音乐课上了
the kids are going to lose their music program.
等我选上学校董事会 就会有的
Eh, just until I'm elected to the school board.
-什么  -没错 我要竞选
What? - Yeah, I'm going to run.
好啊 看来你还是我认识的酷姐儿
OK. Maybe you are still a badass.
当出现不合理的事情的时候
You know, somebody has to be on that board
总有人要在董事会拨乱反正
to push back when things don't make sense.
康纳家的人加入学校董事会
A Conner on the school board.
就好像纵火犯加入了消防队啊
That's like an arsonist joining the fire department.
谁能想到呢
Who would've thunk?
我们干嘛要来宿舍楼
Why are we walking through the dorm?
我知道贝基姨妈只是随机去一个宿舍蹭床睡
I know Aunt Becky just naps in random rooms.
女孩子这样做很迷人
It's charming when a woman does it,
但如果是个男人 我最后
but when a guy does it, you end up
会上变态黑名单的吧
on some kind of list.
其实
Actually
这间房是你的了
this room is yours.
什么 怎么会
What? But how?
我们付不起啊
We can't afford this.
天哪 不会是有人死在这儿了吧
Oh, jeez, did someone die in here?
看看谁矫情得需要一间没死过人的房间了
Oh, look who suddenly needs a room that nobody died in.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你想要住宿舍 恭喜咯
You wanted a dorm room, so congratulations.
你现在正式成为
You are now officially
夜间宿管了
the dorm's night janitor.
这诡异游戏真人秀里 我还有别的选择吗
Is there a door number two on this very weird game show?
没有
No.
不过这是件好事
But this is a good thing.
做学生宿舍管理员 你就能住宿舍了
Being a student janitor, you get a dorm room,
还能挣点钱勤工俭学
you get a small salary for work study,
不用再走读了
no more commuting,
你就有各种时间当同性恋了
and you're going to have all kinds of time to be gay.
我知道这不完美
Look, I know it's not perfect,
但这是我能想到最好的解决办法了
but it's the best thing I could come up with.
不管怎样你还是给了我一间宿舍
Well, you did get me a dorm room.
我也没专门说 别让我去当宿管
And I didn't specifically say, "Don't make me a janitor, "
这也怪我
so that's kind of on me.
抱歉我掺和你的私生活
And I'm sorry for getting involved,
可我就是不能眼睁睁看着你不开心而什么都不做
but I just can't watch you be unhappy and not do something.
你们谁是新来的夜间宿管吗
Is one of you the new night janitor?
是他
It's him.
不是吹 但是我给他找的活儿
Not to brag, but I hooked him up.
你有工作人员电梯钥匙吧
You have keys to the service elevator, right?
-可能吧  -太好了
Probably. - Great.
我是凯莱布 隔壁第二个房间
I'm Caleb. I'm, like, two rooms down.
我们的啤酒桶太多了 搬不上房顶
We have too many kegs to carry up to the roof.
我们要在楼上办派对
We're having a party up there.
-你也来吧  -好啊
You should stop by. Sure.
心理医生对你的评价是错的
The shrink was wrong about you.
你也不是一个彻头彻尾的自恋狂魔
You aren't a total narcissist who is more worried
只想着解决自己身为父母对孩子的愧疚
about absolving yourself of parental guilt
而不是真的解决我的问题
than solving my problems.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
开玩笑呢 是我编的
Kidding. I made that up.
可你这一通说得也太顺嘴了
Yeah, but you did it so fast.
牛排好吃吗
How do you like your steak?
好极了 谢谢
It's great. Thanks.
达琳在你的心理治疗中
So what else is Darlene complaining about
还说了什么
in her sessions?
她把责任全怪在你身上
She's totally victimizing over you
说你干的家务不够多 虽然听上去
not doing enough housework, even though it sounds like
你已经够忙的了
you have your hands full with work,
上班 上学 还有女儿要管
school, and your daughter.
就是啊
I do!
她根本不把整理房间当作家务活
She doesn't think straightening up is housework,
可我觉得把家里的东西
but I think things look neater
垂直摆放 看上去会整洁很多
when they're stacked in at right angles.
你确定她今天不上班吧
You're sure she's off today, right?
所以 以我去健身房的时候
So she's resentful when I take time
她真的会怨气冲天吗
to go to the gym, isn't she?
是的
Yes.
她说你可以享受本的私人时光
She says it's OK for you to have Ben Time,
但她就不能享受达琳的时光
but she doesn't take Darlene Time.
我倒希望她能好好享受达琳时光
Oh, I wish she would take Darlene Time
因为那对我来说就是本的享受时光
because let me tell you, that is Ben Time.